{
    "subject": "Marco_Ferreri",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "L'udienza",
    "human_readable": "Marco Ferreri created L'udienza.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7927327156066895,
            "question": "Who created the film L'udienza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6633689999580383,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5206636190414429,
            "question": "When was L'udienza released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5184727907180786,
            "question": "Who are some actors who appeared in L'udienza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4387320578098297,
            "question": "Is Marco Ferreri known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3876367211341858,
            "question": "Where was L'udienza filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.385757178068161,
            "question": "What is the plot of L'udienza about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36692336201667786,
            "question": "What genre is L'udienza likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3440191447734833,
            "question": "What awards did L'udienza win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28483840823173523,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marco Ferreri created L'udienza.",
            "html": "yago_8396_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards did L'udienza win?",
            "html": "yago_8396_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is L'udienza likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_8396_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of L'udienza about?",
            "html": "yago_8396_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8396_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all three documents mention Marco Ferreri, and one of them specifically mentions that he directed the film \"L'Udienza\" (in document 9.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the creation of the film \"L'udienza\" by Marco Ferreri. For instance, file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_8396/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt mentions the director and cast of the movie, while other files provide details about Marco Ferreri's career and notable works, including \"L'udienza.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}